Denenberg, Tia Schneider Arbitration Files 6275
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United Airlines & AFA, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- UAL and AFA Patricia Robinson, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- UAL/AFA Robinson, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- united Airlines and IAMAW, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Village of Wappinger's Falls and Wappinger's Falls Police Benevolent Assoc., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Wappinger's Falls and PBA, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Wappinger's Fall and CSEA, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- United State Postal Service Redress Materials (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Bell Atlantic NJ and IBEW 827, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- BIC Corporation & United Steelworkers of America, Local 134L, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- NYC Board of Education vs Paula Frankel (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Frankel Transcripts (Continued) (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Health Care alliance, Inc., 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- American Airlines - APFA, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Bell Atlantic - New Jersey, Inc. and IBEW Local 827, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Verizon - NJ and IBEW, Local 827 Cynthia Swanson - 10day suspension, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- BIC Corp and United Steelworkers, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Coca cola and Teamsters 1035, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Engelhard and IBEW, Local 1430, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Lucent Technologies and IBEW Local 827, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Lucent Technologies and IBEW Local 827, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Lucent Technologies and IBEW Local 827, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Lucent Technologies and IBEW Local 827, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Lucent Technologies and IBEW Local 827, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Heinz, USA and UFCW Local 325, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Hope House and AFSCME, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers and League of Off-Broadway Theatres and Producers, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Marlborough Board of Education and Connecticut Education Association, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- NYC Board of Education and UFT, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- NYS (SUNY Buffalo) and UUP Hunter Carrick, Grvnt, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- NYS SUNY Buffalo and UUP, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- NYS Liquor Authority and Joseph G. Williams (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Peekskill City School district and Educational Secretaries, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- United Air Lines and AFA, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- United Airlines and AFA Chamberlain, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- UAL and IAM, Discharge of Dinga, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- United Airlines & IAMAW JFK (Scaccio Discharge), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- United Airlines & AFA Sharon Sikora, GRVNT, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- United Airlines/AFA - Sikora Transcript (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Visitng Nurse Assoc. and NYS Nurses Assoc., 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Visiting Nurse Assoc. of Schenectady County and NYSNA Exhibits (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Watkins Glen Faculty Ass. & Watkins Glen Central School, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- WFSB and NABET, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- WFSB and NABET Disciplinary Letter (Box 17, Folder 11)
- WFSB/NABET - Warner Hutton Grunt (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Atlantic Se Airways and AFA, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Southeast Airways & AFA, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Berlin (Liebenow) PERB, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Callahan Industries, Inc. And IUOE Local 106 FMCS, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Coca-Cola & Teamsters, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Freeport TA and UFSD, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Local 1336, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- +Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Local 1336, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Kennedy Valve and IAMAW FMCS Elmira, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Nassau Regional OTB & IBT, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Nassau OTB and IBT, Local 858, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- New Britain Boe & New Britain Federation of Teachers United Airlines & IAMAW, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Rondout Valley Central School District vs. William F. Cafiero, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Rondout Valley Central school District and William F. Cafiero, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Rondout Valley Central School district and William F. Cafiero Transcripts and Submissions, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- rondout Valley Central School District and William F. Cafiero Transcripts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- United Airlines & IAMAW, 141-M, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- united Airlines & IAMAW District 141-M, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- United Airlines & IAMAW District 141-M, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- PEF and USWA, AFL-CIO, Local 9265Grievance: Class Action, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Verizon Connecticut Solutions and IBEW, Local 827, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Verizon New Jersey Inc. & Local 827 IBEW, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- American Museum of Natural History and Local 1559, DC 37 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Ansonia Coppers & Porass + USWA 6445 New Bottle, Old Grievance, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Berlex Labs and OCAW Local; grievance 15094, Overtime Pay, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Carthage Teachers' Association - Carthage School District, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- County of Columbia and Local 424, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Duanesberg Teachers and School, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Hartford BD + HFT, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Woodhull - Doctors, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- NYS OMH 8 PEF, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- NYS Division for Youth and PEF, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- NYS DOL + PEF Nathan Klugman, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- NYS Dept of Parole & PEF, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- NYS Dept. of Parole & Pef, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Lenders Bagel Bakery and Local 50, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Logistic of CT and ILR Local 1398, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- New Lebanon district and Teachers, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- NYC and DC 37, Local 2507, AFSCME, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- NYS and PEF (SUNY) Hospital, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- State University of New York (SUNY) Health Science Center Syracuse & Public Employees Federation, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- New York State OMROD & Public Employees Federation, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- NYS Division of Parole and PEF, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- New York State OMROD & Public Employees Federation (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Poland CSD and Teachers AAA/SYR, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- city of Schenectady & AFSCME Co. 66, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Dept. of Veteran Affairs NFFE Local 346, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- VA NFFE, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- NYS Dept. of Parole and PEF, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- County of Saratoga and Deputy Sherriff NY PERB, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- SIM KINS & UPIU, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Star Ledger and Local 8N, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- New England Health Care Employees Union, District 1199, SEIU/AFL-CIO and West Wynde Nursing Center, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- ARI, Inc. and NEHCEU, District 1199, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Arlington Central School District and New York State Nurses Association PERB - Fact Finding, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Bell Atlantic - NJ and Local 827, IBEW, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Bell Atlantic & IBEW, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Bell Atlantic NJ/IBEW 827, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Bic Corp + Steelworkers, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Big V Supermarkets, Inc. & UFCW Local 1500, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Center for Optimum Care & 1199 Shannon Harrell (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Champion and UPIU Local 56, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Champion International UPIU Local 45, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Clinton County and CSEA NY PERB, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Corwood Labs and Local 300-S, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Engelhard COPR/IBEW 1430, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Wyandanch Teachers and Schools, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Wyandanch Union Free School District & Wyandanch Teachers Association, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- State of NY and PEF, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Power Conversion and IUE 475, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- TCI of Northern NJ and IBEW 827, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- UTICA and IBEW Local 182 PERB, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Bethlehem Central school District & James & Kathleen Economides on behalf of Mark Economides Impartial hearing Settlement, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Bethlehem Central School district & James and Kathleen Economides on behalf of Mark Economides Impartial Hearing - Settlement, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Bethlehem Central School District 7 James & Kathleen Economides on behalf of Mark Economides Impartial Hearing - Settlement, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Bethlehem Central School district & James & Kathleen Economides on behalf of Mark Economides Impartial Hearing - Settlement, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- American Airlines and APFA, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- American Airlines & APFA Article 3H, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Brunswick Golf and Local 247 IUE, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Greater Hartford Red Cross and Local 3145, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Handy & Harmon and USW, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- NJ Bell Telephone and IBEW Local 827, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- NJ Bell and IBEW Local 827, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- PEF and NYS DOL, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- New York Telephone and CWA, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- PAN AM and ALPA, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- PAN AM/ ALPA Astor (Box 24, Folder 11)
- PAN AM - ASTOR (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Trap Rock + Local 445 IBT Grunt - Capadonna, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Ulster CTY and UC Sheriffs Assoc., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- NYC Board of Education & UFT, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- NYCBOE and UFT, Local 2, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- NYCDOE & UFT, Local 2, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- NYCDOE & UFT, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- NYC Health & Hospital Corp. & Local 420, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- NYC Housing Authority & District Counsel 37, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- OLR & District Counsel 37 OCB, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- OLD and District council 37 OCB Case No. A10197-03, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- NYC Office of Labor Relations & Local 371, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Office of Labor Relations and social Service Employees Union, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- NYS Div. of Housing and Community Renewal & PEF, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NYS Banking Dept. & PEF, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NYS Banking Department & Public employees Federation, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- NYS Banking Department & Public Employees Federation, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- State of New York & Public Employees Federation, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- NYS (Dept. of Taxation & Finance) & PEF, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NYS OMRDD and CSEA GOER/Linda Ronda, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Saint-Gobain Abrasives, Inc. & PACE Local 1-0017, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- NYS (SUNY College at Buffalo) & United University Professions, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Sound Shore Medical Center of Westchester & NYSA, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Verizon Connected Solutions Inc. & IBEW Local 827, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Verizon & IBEW 827, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Yale University & Federation of University Employees, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Misc Tia Denenberg (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Local 5004 - Hospital Professionals and Allied Employees of New Jersey AFT/AFL-CIO and Englewood Hospital & Medical Center, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Roosevelt Board of education and the Roosevelt Teachers Association, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- USAIR The Air Line Pilots Agreement (Box 26, Folder 9)
- USAIR Flight Attendant Agreement (Box 26, Folder 10)
- the city School district of Rochester, New York and the Rochester Teachers Association, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Ingersoll-Rand Company Phillipsburg New Jersey and United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Ingersoll-Dresser Pump company - United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Textile Workers Union Local 1822 - Kraft General Foods Fulton Plant, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- American Home Foods, Inc. and UFCW, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Shop Rules and Absentee Policy, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- New Britain board of Education and the New Britain Federation of Teachers Local 871, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Kennedy Valve - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America(UE) and Local 329, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- The Civil Service Employee Association, Inc. - The State of New York, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- The Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. - The State of New York, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- the Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. - the State of New York, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- United Airlines Flight Attendant Agreement, 1987-1996 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- United Airlines Flight Attendant Agreement, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- United airlines Flight Attendant Agreement, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- United Airlines Flight Attendant Agreement, 1987-1996 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Edward Juliette McMahon, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Edward McMahon (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Where's the Fat NYS Travel Abuse (Box 26, Folder 28)
- William Radacinski, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Pa Dept. of Corrections (Box 26, Folder 30)
- NYS Division of Parole Closing Statement In Matter of PEF vs Parole (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Cassette (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Saratoga + freighters - City Brief (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Actors Equity Association Agreement (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Affiliated Food Distributors and IBT, Local 229 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Allied Chemical Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 12457, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- American Totalisator Co., Inc. and IBEW, Local 1501, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- The Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Union AFL-CIO, CLC, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- City of Amsterdam, New York and Amsterdam Police Benevolent Association, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Ansonia Bd. Of Education and Ansonia Fed. Of Tchrs, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Ansonia Federation of Teachers Negotiating Committee - Ansonia Board of Education Negotiating Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- the Arlington Central School district and The Arlington Teachers Association, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- BASF Wyandotte Corporation, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- BASF Wyandotte Corporation and ICWU, Local 227, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Bay Shore Union Free Schl. Dist. And Bay Shore Classroom Tchrs. Assn., 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Beacon, City of and CSEA Local 814 - Duchess Cty., 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Bensalem Township Schl. District and Bensalem Tnship Educ. Assn., 1978-1981 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Bensalem Township Education Association and Bensalem Township School district, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- the Board of Education Berkshire Farm Union Free School District and The Berkshire Farm Teacher's Association, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Bloomfield Board of Education and Bloomfield Educ. Assn., 1981-1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- BOCES and United Staff Assn., 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Boston Strut company and American guild of Variety Artists, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  May 1
- Cape Cod Hospital and Mass. Hospital Wkrs. Union, Local 880 - SEIU Labor Agreement, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Catskill Central School dist. And Catskill Tchrs. Assn., 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Central Islip Bd. Of Education and Central Islip Bldg. Princ., 1976-1979 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Central Islip Bd. Of Education and Central Islip tchrs. Assn., 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Chesapeake & Potomac Tele. Co. and communications Workers of America General Agreement, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Chicago Markets, Inc. and UFCW, Local One, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Civil Service Reform Act of 1978 Public Law 95-454, Title VII (Box 27, Folder 26)
- combustion Engineering, Inc. and Int'l Bro. Boilermakers, etc., 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Community Legal Services, Inc. & NUHHCE, 1199C, 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- CBA between Community Service Society - District 1199 National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees RWDSU/AFL-CIO, 1982- 1984 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Connecticut, State of and CT Clerical Employees Union AFSCME, Council 14, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Connecticut, State of and CSEA, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Connecticut and SVFT, Local 1797 contract, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Connecticut, State of and SVFT, Local 1797, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Consolidated cigar cor. And Teamsters, Local 401, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- corrugated Box Industry and UPIU, Local No. 381, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- CP Chemicals, Inc. and CP Chemical Workers Union (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Dorr-Oliver Incorporated and IAMAW, District No. 152, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Dresser Manufacturing Division (Dresser Industries) and IAMAW, Local 1965, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. and Transport Workers Union, Local 553 flight Attendants Agreement, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Eastern Air Lines, Inc. and Transport Wkrs. Union, Local 553, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  July 1
- East Ramapo Bd. Of Education and East Ramapo Tchrs. Assn., 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Foreign Policy Assn. Inc. and Newspaper Guild of New York (Box 27, Folder 42)
- General Battery Corporation - Local 5227 United Steel Workers of America, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Gundry, A.R., Inc. and OCAW, Local 8-709, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Hempstead General Hospital and District 1199 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- ITT World Communications, Inc. and Communications Workers of America Agreement, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Jordan Hospital Plymouth, MA Memo of Agreement, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  Nov 29
- Juniata Valley Tri-County Mental Health/Mental Retardation Program and AFSCME, Local 3114, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Kingston City of and Kingston Professional fire Fighters, Local 461, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Contract Between Office and Professional employees International Union, AFL-CIO Local 329 and Knights of Columbus, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Knights of Columbus and OPEIU, Local 329, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  Nov 1
- Lawrence Board of Education and Lawrence Teachers Assn. Agreement, 1978-1981 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Lawrence Board of Education and Lawrence Teachers Assn. Agreement, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and District 1199, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Lederle Laboratories Division of American Cyanamid company and Int'l Chemical Wkrs. Union, Local 143 Agreement, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Lender's Bagel Bakery, Inc. and Confectionery Workers Union Agreement, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Lenders Bagel Bakery, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Wkrs. Int'l, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  June 6
- Lender's Bagel Bakery, Inc. and confectionery Workers Union Local 50, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  Jan 1
- Local 50 Bakery & Confectionery Workers' Union (Box 27, Folder 59)
- The Lockheed-Georgia Company The Aeronautical Machinists Local Lodge 709 The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 60)
- Lone Star Cement, Inc. and Int'l Bro. of Boilermakers (Cement, Lime Wkrs.), 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Lydia E. Hall Hospital and District 1199 National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees - Agreement, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- The Greater Hartford Chapter of The American Red Cross - Local 3145 of council No. 4 of The American Federation of State County & Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Eltra corporation Plant Rules & Regulations (Box 27, Folder 64)
- Lockheed - Georgia Company Vacation Scheduling and Payment (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Mack-Allied Corporation Plant Rules and Regulations (Box 27, Folder 66)
- New York State Thruway Acts Interfering w/ Thruway Operations (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Pathmark (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Republic Airlines and the Federal Aviation Act (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Bloomfield Schools Teacher Evaluation System (Box 27, Folder 70)
- C & P Telephone company of Maryland Providing Accurate & Pleasing Serv. (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Chicago Markets Regulations & Policy Handbook (Box 27, Folder 72)
- CP Chemicals Interpersonal Relations & Behavioral Rules and Regs. (Box 27, Folder 73)
- Dresser Industries Insurance (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Pennsylvania, commonwealth of Handbook of Travel Regulations (Box 27, Folder 75)
- Penna Liquor control Board Work Rules (Box 27, Folder 76)
- Prestolite Battery Respirators & Lead Exposure (Box 27, Folder 77)
- Septa - Standard Rules of conduct and Procedures (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Westinghous Electric Corporation Rules of Conduct (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Westvaco Personal Protective Equipment (Box 27, Folder 80)
- CBA covering Doctors Council Clinicians for the period Jul 1, 1962 to June 30, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 81)
- Bridgeport Board of Education - Bridge port Education Association, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 82)
- Ramapo Central School District - Ramapo Teachers Association, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 83)
- CUNO International and UPIU, PACE AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- CUNO International and UPIU, PACE, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- NYS Office of Mental Health and PEF, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Sirkorski Aircraft and Teamsters 1150, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- UAL/IAMAW System Board of Adjustment, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- United airlines and IAMAW, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Uconn Health Center and University Health Professionals (Box 28, Folder 7)
- University of Connecticut and American Association of University Professors (Box 28, Folder 8)
- League of Off -Broadway Theatres & Procedures & Actors Equity Assoc., 2003 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Hospital & NYSNA, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Doane Pet Care & United Food & Commercial Workers Local 888, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Farmland foods, Inc./Carando & UFCW, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- NYCBOE & UFT, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Agreements and Collective Bargaining Agreements - 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Agreements 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Agreements - 1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Agreements - 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Agreements - 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Agreements - 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Agreements - 1989-1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Agreements 1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Mahopac Central School Dist. Board of Education and Mahopac Tchrs. Assn. Agreement, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts and Alliance, AFSCME, SEIU Contract, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts - rules and Regulations of Bd. Of conciliation and Arbitration (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Metropolitan Hospital and Nat'l Union Hosp. & Health Care Employees, 1199C, 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Mid-Atlantic Container Corp. and IBT, Local 1034, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Middlesex Cablevision and IBEW, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Mt Sinai Hospital & New England Health Care Employees Union, district 1199 Agreement, 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Mount Sinai School district & Mt Sinai Tchrs. Assn., 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Mt. Vernon City Schl. District and Mt. Vernon Fed. Of Tchrs, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Nassau community college and Nassau Community college Fed. Of teachers Local 3150, 1979-1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Nassau County and Patrolmen's Benevolent Association contract, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Nassau county and Superior Officers Assn. of Nassau county Police Dept., 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- League of Voluntary Hospitals & Homes of New York & District 1199, National Union of Hospital & Health Care Emp., 1980-1982 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Naval Air Development center and SEIU Local 36 Agreement (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Newburgh City Schl. District and Newburgh Teachers' Assn., 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- New England Engineering Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 16)